Finding Aid for the Anthony C. Beilenson Papers LSC.0391
UCLA Library Special Collections
Anthony C. Beilenson papers
1963-1997
UCLA Library Special Collections
Beilenson, Anthony C.
LSC.0391
123.0 Linear Feet (296 boxes, 39 cartons, and 4 oversize boxes)
Anthony Charles Beilenson was born on Oct. 26, 1932 in New Rochelle, NY; BA, Harvard Univ., 1954; LL.B, Harvard Univ. Law School, 1957; admitted to CA bar in 1957, and began practice in Beverly Hills; worked as counsel, CA State Assembly Committee on Finance and Insurance, 1960; served in CA State Assembly, 1963-66; served in CA State Senate, 1967-76, where he chaired the Senate Committee on Health and Welfare (1968-74) and the Senate Finance Committee (1975-76); authored more than 200 state laws, including the Therapeutic Abortion Act of 1967, the Auto Repair Fraud Act of 1971, and the Funeral Reform Act of 1971; served as a Democrat in the US House of Representatives, 1977-97; became chair of the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence (1989-90), and served on the House Budget Committee (1988-94), and the House Rules Committee; did not stand as a candidate for re-election in 1996.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed audiovisual materials. Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access, unless otherwise noted in a Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942303643606533
Biography
Anthony Charles Beilenson was born on Oct. 26, 1932 in New Rochelle, NY; BA, Harvard Univ., 1954; LL.B, Harvard Univ. Law School, 1957; admitted to CA bar in 1957, and began practice in Beverly Hills; worked as counsel, CA State Assembly Committee on Finance and Insurance, 1960; served in CA State Assembly, 1963-66; served in CA State Senate, 1967-76, where he chaired the Senate Committee on Health and Welfare (1968-74) and the Senate Finance Committee (1975-76); authored more than 200 state laws, including the Therapeutic Abortion Act of 1967, the Auto Repair Fraud Act of 1971, and the Funeral Reform Act of 1971; served as a Democrat in the US House of Representatives, 1977-97; became chair of the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence (1989-90), and served on the House Budget Committee (1988-94), and the House Rules Committee; did not stand as a candidate for re-election in 1996.
Scope and Content
Boxes 1-168 and 4 oversize boxes include legislative bill files, correspondence, memos, newsclippings, campaign materials, reports, and videotapes relating to Beilenson's political career as a CA state assemblyman, state senator, and member of the US House of Representatives.
Related Material
Securing liberal legislation during the Reagan administration [oral history transcript] / Anthony C. Beilenson, interviewee. UCLA Oral History Department interview, c1982. Available at the UCLA Library Special Collections.
Oral history interview with Anthony C. Beilenson [oral history transcript] 1997-1998 / by Susan Douglass Yates. [1998] UCLA Oral History Program. 2 vols. Available at the UCLA Library Special Collections.
Legislators -- United States -- Archives.; Beilenson, Anthony C.--Archives.
- Abortion
  - KABC and Abortion Laws (Box 78, Folder 2-3)
    Scope and Contents note
    Correspondence addressed to KABC editorials from individuals re abortion laws, major issues include therapeutic abortion, legalization of abortion
- Administration
  - Goodbye Events, Honors (Box 125, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, notes re retirement goodbye events, award dinners
  - Honorary Committees, Name Use (Box 125, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, notes, invitations re Honorary Dinner Committees, Fact Sheet on LA Unified schools physical needs
  - Beilenson Barb-101st Congress (Box 126, Folder 4)
    Beilenson Barb Office News 1990-1995
  - Office Administration-Beilenson Barb (Box 126, Folder 5)
    Beilenson Barb Office News 99th Congress
  - Beilenson Barb - 1983-84 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    Beilenson Barb Office News 1983-1984
  - Office Administration-Beilenson Barb (Box 126, Folder 7)
    Beilenson Barb Office News 1979-1982
  - Inner-Office Info-Old Barbs (Box 126, Folder 8)
    Beilenson Barb Office News 1977-1978
  - Truman Award Luncheon (Box 127, Folder 1)
    Large blue photo album "Harry S Truman Award Luncheon honoring Congressman Anthony Beilenson, Sat Jan 28, 1989," Sportsmen's Lodge, Studio City, CA
  - Dolores Beilenson Bio (Box 128, Folder 1)
    Dolores Beilenson biography sheet, schedules 1993-1995, pamphlets such as Jewish Home for The Aging
  - DB Schedule - Nov 1994 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    Notes, Dolores Beilenson biography
  - DB Schedule - Oct 1994 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    Notes, schedule for Oct 1994 for Dolores Beilenson
  - DB Schedule - Sept 1994 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    Memos, notes re schedule for Dolores Beilenson Sept 1994
  - DB Schedule - Aug 1994 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    Notes, American Cancer Society Invitation, press clippings, tele-messages, re schedule for Dolores Beilenson
  - DB Schedule - July 1994 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    Notes, memos, re schedule of Dolores Beilenson July 1994
  - DB Schedule - June 1994 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    Memos, notes, invitations, telephone messages re schedule of Dolores Beilenson
  - DB Schedule - May 1994 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    Memos, notes, tele-messages re schedule for Dolores Beilenson
  - DB Schedule - Mar/Apr 94 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, schedule of Dolores Beilenson March 25- April 17 1994
  - DB Schedule - Jan 1994 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, schedule of Dolores Beilenson Jan 1994
  - DB Schedule - Dec 1993 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    Memos, correspondence, notes schedule of Dolores Beilenson Dec 1993
  - DB Schedule - 1988 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, memo, notes, announcement re schedule of Dolores Beilenson
  - DB Bio & Cookbook (Box 128, Folder 14)
    Notes, biography of Dolores, Cookbook Recipes
  - Dolores Beilenson 84-87 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, schedules, newspaper clippings, photographs, negatives re Dolores Beilenson Schedule, pamphlets
  - Dolores Beilenson Schedule (Box 128, Folder 16)
    Memos, notes, packet entitled "The Arts in The San Fernando Valley", 1980- 81 Valley Gala Symphony Season packet, re schedule for Dolores Beilenson
  - Taft Decathlon 5/94 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes, invitations, tele-messages, newspaper clippings, re Taft High School Decathlon
  - Cal State Northridge University (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, reports, newspaper clippings, tele-messages, re designating Cal State Northridge as A National Higher Education Center on Disability
  - Angeles Pipeline-4 Corners (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, newspaper clippings, agenda, meeting minutes, re Angeles Pipeline
  - Environment & National Resources (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, newspaper clippings, re Environment & Natural Resources Westwood Park, brochure
  - Boxer Hearings (AIDS) (Box 129, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, press releases, remarks, Hearing roster Testimony House Budget Committee, re Barbara Boxer Hearing on AIDS
  - Social Security Disability (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Legislative Bulletins, Legislative reports, correspondence, memos, notes, newspaper clippings re Social Security Disability Benefits Reform
  - HR 6181-Soc Security Disability (Box 130, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, memos, news releases, notes, re HR 6181 Social Security Disability
  - Social Security Disability (Box 130, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, memos, newspaper clippings, notes, conference reports, HR 6181, re Social Security Disability New Amendments
  - Social Security Reform 83 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    Correspondence re Social Security Disability Reform, Insurance Program
  - Social Security Disability (Box 130, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, news releases, notes, memos, re Social Security Disability Reform for Beneficiaries, newspaper clippings
  - Social Security Legislation (Box 130, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, news releases, notes, memos, Handbook for Physicians "Disability Evaluation Under Social Security", agenda re Social Security Disability
  - Social Security Disability (Box 130, Folder 7)
    Legislative information, notice, pamphlet, HR 3755, Mario Lopez
  - SSA Disability Reviews (Box 130, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, news release, Summary of Social Security Student Benefits, Fact Sheets on Disability Amendments of 1982, Fair Reviews for Social Security Disability Recipients
  - ACB District Visit Schedule (Box 131, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, memos, brochures, news releases, schedules
  - ACB District Visit Schedule (Box 131, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, memos, brochures, schedules 1986
  - ACB Schedule 1987 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    ACB Schedule March 20, 1987 - November 2, 1987
  - ACB Schedule 1990 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    ACB Schedule 1/3/90 - 11/11/90, correspondence, memos, brochures
  - ACB Schedule 1991 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    ACB Schedule 1/12/91 - 12/9/91, correspondence, memos, brochures, newspaper clippings
  - ACB Schedule 1992 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    ACB Schedule Jan 1992 - Dec 1992, correspondence, memos, brochures, newspaper clippings, community meetings announcements
  - ACB Schedule 1993 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    ACB Schedule Mar 1993 - Dec 1993 District Visits, correspondence, memos, Community meeting announcements
  - ACB Schedule 1995 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    ACB Schedule Feb 1995 - Nov 1995 District Visits, correspondence, memos, invitations, Community Meetings announcements
  - ACB Schedule May 1994 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    ACB Schedule May 1994, correspondence, memos, telephone messages, invitations
  - ACB Schedule April 1994 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    ACB Schedule April 1994, correspondence, memos, notes, District Visits, community announcements
  - ACB Schedule March 1994 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    ACB Schedule March 1994, correspondence, memos, notes, District Visits, tele-messages, community meeting announcements
  - ACB Schedule Feb 1994 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    ACB Schedule Feb 1994, correspondence, memos, notes, district visits, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Jan 1994 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    ACB Schedule Jan 1994, correspondence, memos, notes, district visits, Invitations, Motion Picture & TV Fund Foundation packet, tele-messages
  - ACB Schedule Oct-Nov 1994 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    ACB Schedule Oct-Nov 1994, correspondence, memos, notes, district visits, Invitations,
  - ACB Schedule Oct 1994 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    ACB Schedule Oct 1994, correspondence, memos, notes, district visits, invitations, news publications
  - ACB Schedule Sept 1994 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    ACB Schedule Sept 1994, district visits, correspondence, memos, notes, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Aug 1994 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    ACB Schedule Aug 1994, district visits, correspondence, memos, notes invitations, tele-messages
  - ACB Schedule July 1994 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    ACB Schedule July 1994, district visits, correspondence, memos, notes, invitations, community meeting announcements
  - ACB Schedule June 1994 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    ACB Schedule June 1994, district visits, correspondence, memos, notes, invitations, tele-messages
  - ACB Schedule Dec 1996 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    Correspondence re invitation to speak re future of health care, Mar 20, 1997
  - ACB Schedule Nov 1996 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, memos, invitations, tele-messages, re ACB Schedule Nov 1996
  - ACB Schedule Oct 1996 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    ACB Schedule Oct 1996, correspondence, memos, announcements, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Sept 1996 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    ACB Schedule, correspondence Sept Aug 1996
  - ACB Schedule Aug 1996 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    ACB Schedule Aug 1996, correspondence, notes, memos, invitations
  - ACB Schedule June 1996 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    ACB Schedule June 1996, correspondence, memos, notes, invitations
  - ACB Schedule July 1996 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    ACB Schedule July 1996, Memo
  - ACB Schedule May 1996 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    ACB Schedule May 1996, memos, correspondence, notes, directions to UCLA Dept Special Collections
  - ACB Schedule April 1996 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    ACB Schedule April 1996, memos, correspondence, notes
  - ACB Schedule March 1996 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    ACB Schedule March 1996, memos, correspondence, notes, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Feb 1996 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    ACB Schedule Feb 1996, correspondence, memos, notes, invitations, brochure by San Fernando Valley Interfaith Council
  - ACB Schedule Jan 1996 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    ACB Schedule Jan 1996, correspondence, memos, notes, invitations, ACB Biography, pamphlet
  - Community Service Guide '84 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    Congressman Beilenson's Community Service Guide 1984 Edition
  - Academy Day - April 1984 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, Fax transmittals for Academy Day Program, flyer, Voucher re Academy Day April 28, 1984
  - Academy Day - 1993 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, news releases, flyer, re Academy Day 1993
  - White House Conference on Aging (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, newsletters, report, calendar, Fact Sheet on Aging, re White House Conference on Aging, seniors
  - White House Conference on Aging (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, newspaper clippings, packet on White House Conference on Aging, seniors, older citizens
  - Reseda Senior Multi Center (Box 142, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, meeting minutes, newsletter The Needs of The Elderly, Reseda Senior Multi-purpose Center
  - support letters (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Correspondence from ACB re support for various organizations, support letters
  - Nice letters (Incoming) (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Correspondence to ACB, nice letters, thank you letters re FEMA, SBA
  - Inauguration 1992-93 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, Fax transmittals re inauguration ceremonies 93
  - Thousand Oaks-Open House (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, Thousand Oaks Guest List, Thousand Oaks Open House Mar 19, 1993
  - Orange Picking-Northridge (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, newspaper clippings, news release re ACB spearheading distribution of 50,000 lbs of oranges, maps of Cal State Northridge, orange picking
  - Yearly Mail Counts (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Yearly Mail Counts
  - Congressional Record Inserts (Box 143, Folder 7)
    Congressional Record Inserts 1977-1984 of ACB re such Fax transmittals as Nuclear Freeze, Foreign Aid Authorization, preventing teenage pregnancy, Soviet Jewry, arms control
  - Key Labor Votes (Box 143, Folder 8)
    Key Labor Votes from Congressional Quarterly Almanac
  - Key Legislative Issues-1982 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, lists of key legislative Fax transmittals 1982 Election, ACB Key Israel/Jewish Co-sponsorships
  - ACB Action List:103rd Congress (Box 144, Folder 1)
    ACB Action on various Fax transmittals 103rd Congress such as agriculture, budget/economic affairs, California, Armed Services, education, energy, health, labor
  - ACB Action List:102 Congress (Box 144, Folder 2)
    ACB Action on various Fax transmittals 102nd Congress such as agriculture, budget, California, environment, education, energy, health
  - Congressional Spouse PSA (Box 148, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, re Dolores Public Service announcements (PSA) on breast cancer, drunk driving
  - Dolores Beilenson Schedule (Box 148, Folder 8)
    Dolores Beilenson's schedules Sept & Oct 1993, notes
  - Dolores' Schedule 7-8/93 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    Dolores Beilenson's schedules July & Aug 1993, newspaper clippings
  - Dolores' Schedule May 93 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    Dolores Beilenson's Schedule May, 1993
  - Dolores' Schedule April 93 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    Dolores Beilenson's Schedule April, 1993
  - Dolores' Schedule Mar 93 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    Dolores Beilenson's Schedule Mar 1993, biography
  - ACB Schedule Jan 1993 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    ACB Schedule January 1993, correspondence
  - ACB Schedule Feb 1993 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    ACB Schedule Feb 1993, correspondence, invitations also to Dolores Beilenson
  - ACB Schedule Mar 1993 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    ACB Schedule Mar 1993, correspondence, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Mar 1993 (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - ACB Schedule April 1993 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    ACB Schedule April 1993, correspondence, invitations, AMGEN annual report, Planned Parenthood invite
  - ACB Schedule May 1993 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    ACB Schedule May 1993, correspondence, memos, invitations, newspaper clipping
  - ACB Schedule May-June 93 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    ACB Schedule May-June 93, correspondence, memos, invitations, newspaper clippings, newsletter
  - ACB Schedule June 1993 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    ACB Schedule June 1993, notes, memos, correspondence, invitations
  - ACB Schedule July 1993 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    ACB Schedule July 1993, correspondence, notes, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Aug 1993 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    ACB Schedule Aug 1993, correspondence, notes, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Sept 1993 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    ACB Schedule Sept 1993, correspondence, notes, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Oct 1993 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    ACB Schedule Oct 1993, correspondence, notes, invitations
  - ACB Schedule Oct 1993 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    ACB Schedule Oct 1993, correspondence, notes, invitations, photograph, community meeting announcements
  - ACB Schedule Dec 1993 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    ACB Schedule Dec 1993, correspondence, notes, invitations, community meeting announcements
  - ACB Schedule Dec 1993 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    ACB Schedule Dec 1993, correspondence, memos, notes, invitations, magazine
  - Canoga Park Day Laborer Problem (Box 149, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, petitions, newspapers, newspaper clippings re Canoga Park, North Hollywood, San Fernando Valley Day Laborer problem
  - Helicopter Noise-Van Nuys (Box 149, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, Van Nuys Airport helicopter traffic patterns map, pilot bulletin re noise abatement, helicopter noise
  - Aircraft Noise-Calabasas (Box 149, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, memo, re aircraft noise over the Calabasas Highlands
  - Canoga-Owensmouth History (Box 149, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, historical notes newsletters, re Canoga-Owensmouth Historical Society
  - Canoga Park Rebuild (Box 149, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, agenda, newspaper clippings, re rebuilding Canoga Park, Revitalization Planning Workshop, Pussycat Theatre
  - Van Nuys Airport (Box 150, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, memos, re Van Nuys Airport Noise Compatibility Program, Draft Master Plan Environmental Impact report, zone change
  - Elsmere Canyon (Box 150, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, newspaper clippings, re waste dump in Elsmere Canyon, landfill opposition
  - Charette (Box 150, Folder 5)
    Agenda, concept paper, re Revitalization Planning Workshop, or "Charette" for Reseda & Canoga Park
  - Energy Tech Engineer Center (Box 150, Folder 6)
    Booklet re Energy Technology Engineering Center, Community Reuse Org, meeting agenda, correspondence, notes
  - Energy Tech Engineer Center (Box 150, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, newsletter, re Los Angeles Community Reuse Organization, Energy Technology Engineering Center
  - Energy Tech Engineer Center (Box 150, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, press releases, newspaper clippings, re LA Community Reuse Organization (CRO) & Dept of energy, Privatization of Energy Technology Engineering Center (ETEC), Rocketdyne
  - Assessment Roll (Box 150, Folder 9)
    Black Booklet entitled "1995-1996 Roll Release" from Kenneth Hahn re Assessment Roll Reflects Decrease Based on Value Index of All Property Assessed in Los Angeles County
  - Guest Book (Box 159, Folder 6)
    Guest book with entries
  - Certificate -"Spirit of The Valley" (Box 161, Folder 1)
    Certificate from The County of Los Angeles re San Fernando Valley Interfaith Council's 1996 "Spirit of The Valley" awarded to Beilenson by Zev Yaroskavsky and Michael D. Antonovich
  - Certificate - Harry S. Truman Award (Box 161, Folder 2)
    Certificate from The City of Los Angeles re Harry S. Truman Award awarded to Tony and Dolores Beilenson by Mayor Tom Bradley
  - Plague - Youth Soccer Organization (Box 161, Folder 3)
    Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The Children of American Youth Soccer Organization
  - Plaque - CCLA (Box 161, Folder 4)
    Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The California Council of Landscape Architects (CCLA)
  - Plaque - CCHA (Box 161, Folder 5)
    Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The Carthay Circle Homeowners Association (CCHA)
  - Plaque - LACC (Box 162, Folder 1)
    Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The Los Angeles Collegiate Council (LACC)
  - Plaque - IJAC (Box 162, Folder 2)
    Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The Iranian Jewish Association of California (IJAC)
  - Plaque - CSHS (Box 162, Folder 3)
    Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The Committee to Save Human Services
  - Plaque - Harry S. Truman Award (Box 162, Folder 4)
    Harry S. Truman Award Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The Democratic Party of San Fernando Valley
  - Plaque - TPOA (Box 162, Folder 5)
    Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The Tarzana Property Owners Association (TPOA) for the establishment of the Santa Monica Mountains National Recreation Area (SMMNRA)
  - Plaque - CPWHC (Box 162, Folder 6)
    Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The Canoga Park/West Hills Chamber for "Lest We Forget" Canoga Park Memorial Day Parade
  - Plaque - Harry S. Truman Award (Box 162, Folder 7)
    Harry S. Truman Award Plaque awarded to Beilenson from The San Fernando Valley Democratic Party
  - Certificate - Harry S. Truman Award (Box 163, Folder 1)
    Certificate from The County of Los Angeles re Harry S. Truman Award awarded to Tony and Dolores Beilenson by Edmund D. Edelman, Chairman of The Board
  - Certificate - Harry S. Truman Award (Box 163, Folder 2)
    Certificate from The California Legislature Assembly re Harry S. Truman Award awarded to Tony and Dolores Beilenson by Terry B. Friedman
- California Coast
  - L.A. County Beaches (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Correspondence re county cutbacks on lifeguards; potential transfer of state beaches to L.A. County Dept of Beaches & Harbors; Friends of California Parks re County cancelling agreement to operate eight state owned beaches; State Park Beach giveaway protested the Friends of The Santa Monica Mountains Parks & Seashore and Sierra Club
- Campaign
  - Primary Election Nite 6/2/92 McClintock/Results and Nov. 3, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, Fax sheets, results, notes, newspaper clippings re the results of the Primary Election on 6/2/1992
  - LA Times Endorsement Interview 10/20/92 @ 2:00 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, notes, newspaper clippings re Los Angeles Times endorsement interview, major issue includes tax cuts
  - LA Times Endorsement Interview 10/20/92 @ 2:00 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Pamphlet re statistics of the Presidential and Congressional Election and re statement of vote compiled by March Fong Eu; correspondence re Salomon for Congress; newspaper clippings re Anti War Vote; journal article re Anthony Beilenson
  - 24th CD-ACB (1) (Box 1, Folder 12)